<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 01:46:31 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Channel Force Closures</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/understanding-channel-force-closures/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 01:46:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/understanding-channel-force-closures/</guid>
      
        <description>It took me forever to fully understand the intricacies of channel force closures. Sources online were either too high level or too specific about implementation details - this post aims to be an in-between. The content of this post dives into the transactions of a force closure. This post will answer specific questions like:
What are the outputs in a commitment transaction? What transactions will be broadcasted onchain? Cooperative Channel Close To start, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about cooperative channel closures, when life is roses and butterflies.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuck Payments on the Lightning Network</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/stuck-payments-on-the-lightning-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:58:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/stuck-payments-on-the-lightning-network/</guid>
      
        <description>Happy Halvening day! The fees in the network as of writing this article is insane. So many inscriptions in this block.
(Friday, April 19, 2024, at 5:39 pm PST via mempool.space)
While the lightning network is being battle tested in the high fee environment, I want to point out another issue with lightning. A bigger and more fundamental issue that I don&amp;rsquo;t see many people talking about - stuck payments.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://example.org/writing/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/writing/hello-world/</guid>
      
        <description>For the longest time, I thought about creating my own space where I can write whatever I want. Throughout the years I&amp;rsquo;ve written on Medium and Substack.
So why not use those instead?
Substack provided a good environment to post whatever I wanted. However, the issue I found with Subastack was that it was difficult for people to find it. On the other hand, while, Medium has a wonderful community of readers and writers, there were some posts where I wanted to share half baked ideas without having to worry about feedback from others.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash App Investing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:44:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/investing/</guid>
      
        <description>I was the founding server engineer of Cash App Investing LLC, a new business unit created within Cash App. We built a fully fledged self-directed trading product from MVP to serving 8+ million customers.
The Problem According to Gallop, in 2018, only 55% of Americans owned stock.
Similarly a study from Blackrock showed that 57% out of 27,000 interviewees did not own stock.
That means roughly half of the population did not allocate their wealth in assets, and instead kept their money in either cash under their beds or a low interest-rate savings account.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash App Bitcoin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/bitcoin/</guid>
      
        <description>It was a blast working on our Bitcoin product which, in my biased opinion, is the simplest product in the U.S for trading, withdrawing and depositing Bitcoin.
I helped to further the Bitcoin mission by making Bitcoin more usable as a currency, specifically integrating the lightning network into Cash App via LDK.
The Problem Bitcoin is a unique asset that the world has never seen before. Bitcoin is also seen as a currency because the network is used as a payment system.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home VPN</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/vpn/</guid>
      
        <description>During my travels abroad, I wanted to access websites which were blocked in certain countries. A VPN provider like NordVPN would do the job, but I wanted something with more privacy. Historically, there have been data breaches within VPN providers. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to trust whether VPN providers actually keep logs, sell our data or monitor our traffic. It&amp;rsquo;s totally possible that if they can profit or have to protect themselves, they with share them with other companies.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConNextor</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/connextor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/connextor/</guid>
      
        <description>I co-founded ConNextor with Elva Young and David Song during ours studies at the University of Waterloo.
The mission was to connect students from different disciplines to collaborate on projects together. Hackathons are a great platform to meet people and hack on things in a short time frame, but we found that most projects stopped progress after the hackathon. We wanted to foster collaboration for longer term projects.
ConNextor was a social platform for students to gain and track experiences by collaborating on projects together.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fun/</guid>
      
        <description>Stand-Up I feel alive when I&amp;rsquo;m on stage. Video Making Videos are just another form of storytelling. Need to explore deeper here.
Favorite Quotes &amp;ldquo;You have to dance beautifully in the box that you&amp;rsquo;re comfortable dancing in. My box was to be extremely ambitious within the sport of basketball. Your box is different than mine. Everybody has their own. It&amp;rsquo;s your job to try to perfect it and make it as beautiful of a canvas as you can make it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/speaking/</guid>
      
        <description>Public Speaking I was obsessed with sharpening my public speaking skills in 2021.
In May 2023, I represented San Francisco in the Bay Area wide toastmasters public speaking competition. I made it to the top 6 finalists out of 100 clubs in the Bay Area.
I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done this without my amazing toastmasters club, Everybody Speaks. Special thanks to the club presidents Levgeniia, James and Pam.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>