<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineerings on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineerings on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:44:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cash App Investing</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:44:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/investing/</guid>
      
        <description>I was the founding server engineer of Cash App Investing LLC, a new business unit created within Cash App. We built a fully fledged self-directed trading product from MVP to serving 8+ million customers.
The Problem According to Gallop, in 2018, only 55% of Americans owned stock.
Similarly a study from Blackrock showed that 57% out of 27,000 interviewees did not own stock.
That means roughly half of the population did not allocate their wealth in assets, and instead kept their money in either cash under their beds or a low interest-rate savings account.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash App Bitcoin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/bitcoin/</guid>
      
        <description>It was a blast working on our Bitcoin product which, in my biased opinion, is the simplest product in the U.S for trading, withdrawing and depositing Bitcoin.
I helped to further the Bitcoin mission by making Bitcoin more usable as a currency, specifically integrating the lightning network into Cash App via LDK.
The Problem Bitcoin is a unique asset that the world has never seen before. Bitcoin is also seen as a currency because the network is used as a payment system.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home VPN</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/vpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/vpn/</guid>
      
        <description>During my travels abroad, I wanted to access websites which were blocked in certain countries. A VPN provider like NordVPN would do the job, but I wanted something with more privacy. Historically, there have been data breaches within VPN providers. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to trust whether VPN providers actually keep logs, sell our data or monitor our traffic. It&amp;rsquo;s totally possible that if they can profit or have to protect themselves, they with share them with other companies.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConNextor</title>
      <link>http://example.org/engineering/connextor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/engineering/connextor/</guid>
      
        <description>I co-founded ConNextor with Elva Young and David Song during ours studies at the University of Waterloo.
The mission was to connect students from different disciplines to collaborate on projects together. Hackathons are a great platform to meet people and hack on things in a short time frame, but we found that most projects stopped progress after the hackathon. We wanted to foster collaboration for longer term projects.
ConNextor was a social platform for students to gain and track experiences by collaborating on projects together.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>